Finding Aid for the Robert A. McGaw Map Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Robert A. McGaw Map Collection
1760-1926
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0274
1 linear_feet
- New Map of Cherokee Nation, [1760]; 1; ID: 1 Map #: 001 Map Title: New Map of Cherokee Nation Date of Creation: [1760] Cartographer: Engraver: Thomas Kitchin Place of Publication: London Publisher: Source of Information: London Magazine Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 7x9 Notes: Engraved from an Indian draught Framed: Yes Location: Top Drawer
- Draught of Cherokee Country, 1762; 2; ID: 2 Map #: 002 Map Title: Draught of Cherokee Country Date of Creation: 1762 Cartographer: Henry Timberlake Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Memoirs of Lt. H. Timberlake Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 15.5x9.5 Notes: Lists towns with their chiefs and number of warriors Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- New Map of N. and S. Carolina and Georgia, ca. 1765; 3; ID: 3 Map #: 003 Map Title: New Map of N. and S. Carolina and Georgia Date of Creation: ca. 1765 Cartographer: Thomas Kitchin Engraver: Place of Publication: London Publisher: Source of Information: London Magazine Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 6.5x9 Notes: Shows Indian territories east of the Mississippi Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Sketch of the Cherokee Country, [1772]; 4; ID: 4 Map #: 004 Map Title: Sketch of the Cherokee Country Date of Creation: [1772] Cartographer: Engraver: J. Lodge Place of Publication: London Publisher: Source of Information: Mant's "History of the War in America" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 10.75x15.75 Notes: Only known copy in any Tennessee collection Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Il Paese De Cherachesi, ca. 1780; 5; ID: 5 Map #: 005 Map Title: Il Paese De Cherachesi Date of Creation: ca. 1780 Cartographer: Antonio Zatta Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Atlante Novissimo Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 12.5x17 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Map of the States of Va, N.C., S.C. and Ga, ca. 1791; 6; ID: 6 Map #: 006 Map Title: Map of the States of Va, N.C., S.C. and Ga Date of Creation: ca. 1791 Cartographer: Joseph Purcell Engraver: Amos Dolittle Place of Publication: Boston Publisher: John Stockdale Source of Information: Jedidiah Morse's "Geography" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 12.5x15 Notes: Shows "Country of Frankland" in E. Tennessee Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Map of the States of Va., N.C., S.C., and Ga., 1792; 7; ID: 7 Map #: 007 Map Title: Map of the States of Va., N.C., S.C., and Ga. Date of Creation: 1792 Cartographer: Joseph Purcell Engraver: W. Harrison, Sr., Jr. Place of Publication: London Publisher: John Stockdale Source of Information: Jedidiah Morse's "Geography" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 12.25x14.5 Notes: Shows "Country of Frankland" in E. Tennessee Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Map of the Tennassee Government (state) formerly Part of N.C., [1794]; 8; ID: 8 Map #: 008 Map Title: Map of the Tennassee Government (state) formerly Part of N.C. Date of Creation: [1794] Cartographer: Daniel Smith and others Engraver: J.T. Scott Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Mathew Carey Source of Information: General Atlas for Carey's "Edition of Gutherie's Geography Improved" Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 9.75x20.5 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Map of the Tennessee Government, 1794; 9; ID: 9 Map #: 009 Map Title: Map of the Tennessee Government Date of Creation: 1794 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: London Publisher: J. Stockdale Source of Information: Jedidiah Morse's "American Geography" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 6.5x9.25 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Top Drawer
- Map of the State of Kentucky; with Adjoining Territories, 1794; 10; ID: 10 Map #: 010 Map Title: Map of the State of Kentucky; with Adjoining Territories Date of Creation: 1794 Cartographer: J. Russell Engraver: Place of Publication: London Publisher: H.C. Symonds Source of Information: Winterbotham's "History" and Russell's "American Atlas" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 15x18 Notes: Shows Tennessee as the Southwest Territory with areas "Reserved for the N.C. Troops" Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- S.W. Territory, [1795, 1796]; 11; ID: 11 Map #: 011 Map Title: S.W. Territory Date of Creation: [1795, 1796] Cartographer: Joseph Scott Engraver: Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: F.andR. Bailey Source of Information: Joseph Scott's "The U.S. Gazetteer: An Atlas of the United States" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 6x7 Notes: Mero District shown "Nash ville and "Tennassee" River located Framed: Yes Location: Top Drawer
- A Map of the Tennassee Government, 1795; 12; ID: 12 Map #: 012 Map Title: A Map of the Tennassee Government Date of Creation: 1795 Cartographer: Engraver: B. Tanner Place of Publication: New York Publisher: J. Reid, L. Wagland, and C. Smith Source of Information: William Winterbotham's "The American Atlas, 1796" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 7x15 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Tennassee: lately the S.W. Territory, [1796]; 13; ID: 13 Map #: 013 Map Title: Tennassee: lately the S.W. Territory Date of Creation: [1796] Cartographer: Mathew Carey Engraver: W. Barker Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Mathew Carey Source of Information: Carey's "American Pocket Atlas" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 5.5x7.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- A Map of the State of Kentucky and the Tennessee Government, [1796]; 14; ID: 14 Map #: 014 Map Title: A Map of the State of Kentucky and the Tennessee Government Date of Creation: [1796] Cartographer: Cyrus Harris Engraver: A. Dolittle Place of Publication: Boston Publisher: Thomas and Andrews Source of Information: Jedidiah Morse's "American Universal Geography" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 7.5x11.2 5 Notes: Includes atlas entry on Tennessee Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- A Map of Tennassee State formerly part of North Carolina, [1796]; 15; ID: 15 Map #: 015 Map Title: A Map of Tennassee State formerly part of North Carolina Date of Creation: [1796] Cartographer: Daniel Smith Engraver: J.T. Scott Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Mathew Carey Source of Information: Carey's "American Edition of Guthrie's Geography Improved" Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 9.25x20.5 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- A Topographical Description of the Western Territory of N. America, 1797, 3rd ed.; 16; ID: 16 Map #: 016 Map Title: A Topographical Description of the Western Territory of N. America Date of Creation: 1797, 3rd ed. Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: London Publisher: J. Debrett Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 8.25x5 Notes: Author: Gilbert Imlay Format is a book. Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Map of the Southern Parts of the U.S. of America, [1797]; 17; ID: 17 Map #: 017 Map Title: Map of the Southern Parts of the U.S. of America Date of Creation: [1797] Cartographer: Abraham Bradley Jr. Engraver: S. Hill Place of Publication: Boston Publisher: Source of Information: Jedidiah Morse's "American Gazetteer" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 8x15.25 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Tennassee, ca. 1800; 18; ID: 18 Map #: 018 Map Title: Tennassee Date of Creation: ca. 1800 Cartographer: Joseph Scott Engraver: Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Francis and Robert Bailey Source of Information: "The New and Universal Gazetteer" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 6x7.25 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- A Map of the Tennassee Govt. from the latest Surveys, 1799; 19; ID: 19 Map #: 019 Map Title: A Map of the Tennassee Govt. from the latest Surveys Date of Creation: 1799 Cartographer: Daniel Smith Engraver: John Payne Place of Publication: New York Publisher: Low and Willis Source of Information: "A New and Complete System of Universal Geography" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 7x15 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- The State of Kentucky with the adjoining Territories, 1800; 20; ID: 20 Map #: 020 Map Title: The State of Kentucky with the adjoining Territories Date of Creation: 1800 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: New York Publisher: I. Low Source of Information: "Payne's Geography" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 7.5x8.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Tennessee, [1804]; 21; ID: 21 Map #: 021 Map Title: Tennessee Date of Creation: [1804] Cartographer: Samuel Lewis Engraver: Lawson Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: J. Conrad and Co. Source of Information: "A New and Elegant General Atlas" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 8x10 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Top Drawer
- Nashville in 1804, 22; ID: 22 Map #: 022 Map Title: Nashville in 1804 Date of Creation: [1804] Cartographer: W.A. Eifhbaum Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 11x13.5 Notes: Facsimile of map done for A.W. Putnam's "History of Middle Tennessee"? Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Tennassee: lately the S.W. Territory, [1805]; 23; ID: 23 Map #: 023 Map Title: Tennassee: lately the S.W. Territory Date of Creation: [1805] Cartographer: Mathew Carey Engraver: W. Barker Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Mathew Carey Source of Information: Carey's "American Pocket Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 6x8 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Middle Drawer
- United States of America, 1809; 24; ID: 24 Map #: 024 Map Title: United States of America Date of Creation: 1809 Cartographer: John Luffman Engraver: Place of Publication: London Publisher: John Luffman Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 8.75x8 Notes: Shows East and Middle Tennessee as the State of Cumberland and West Tennessee, Alabama and Mississippi as the State of Tennessee Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- A Map of the Tennassee Govt. from The Surveys, 1810; 25; ID: 25 Map #: 025 Map Title: A Map of the Tennassee Govt. from The Surveys Date of Creation: 1810 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: New York Publisher: E. Low Source of Information: Low's "New and Complete American Encyclopedia " Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 7x15 Notes: Last of the series of maps based on Daniel Smith's surveys in 1794 Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Tennessee, [1813]; 26; ID: 26 Map #: 026 Map Title: Tennessee Date of Creation: [1813] Cartographer: Mathew Carey Engraver: Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Mathew Carey Source of Information: "Carey's American Pocket Atlas" Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 6x7.5 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Top Drawer
- The State of Tennessee, [1814]; 27; ID: 27 Map #: 027 Map Title: The State of Tennessee Date of Creation: [1814] Cartographer: Mathew Carey Engraver: Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Mathew Carey Source of Information: Carey's "General Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 9x20 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- The State of Tennessee, [1817]; 28; ID: 28 Map #: 028 Map Title: The State of Tennessee Date of Creation: [1817] Cartographer: Mathew Carey Engraver: Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Mathew Carey and Son Source of Information: Carey's "General Atlas" Color/Black and White: outline in color Size of Map: 9.5x20.5 Notes: Revised from the map of Tennessee published in "Carey's General Atlas" in 1814, 1815, and 1816 Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Compiled from the Latest Authorities, ca. 1825; 29; ID: 29 Map #: 029 Map Title: Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Compiled from the Latest Authorities Date of Creation: ca. 1825 Cartographer: D.H. Vance Engraver: Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Anthony Finley Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 17x21 Notes: Includes table of censuses, ending in 1820. Map folds out of leather binding. Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Map of Tennessee in 1821, ca. 1821; 30; ID: 30 Map #: 030 Map Title: Map of Tennessee in 1821 Date of Creation: ca. 1821 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 5.5x13.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Tennessee, [1822]; 31; ID: 31 Map #: 031 Map Title: Tennessee Date of Creation: [1822] Cartographer: Luke Drury Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Miller and Hutchens Source of Information: "A Geography for Schools" Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 8.5x10 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Geographical, Statistical and Historical Map of Tennessee, [1822]; 32; ID: 32 Map #: 032 Map Title: Geographical, Statistical and Historical Map of Tennessee Date of Creation: [1822] Cartographer: F. Lucas, Jr. Engraver: Kneass Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: H.C. Carey and I. Lea Source of Information: Carey and Lea's "A Complete Historical, Chronological and Geographical American Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 11.25x18.5 Notes: Includes text at bottom with information about the state Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Tennessee, [1823]; 33; ID: 33 Map #: 033 Map Title: Tennessee Date of Creation: [1823] Cartographer: F. Lucas, Jr. Engraver: Place of Publication: Baltimore Publisher: B.T. Welch and Co. Source of Information: Lucas' "General Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 11x18 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Kentucky and Tennessee, [1823]; 34; ID: 34 Map #: 034 Map Title: Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: [1823] Cartographer: Sidney Morse Engraver: N.and S.S. Jocelyn Place of Publication: New Haven Publisher: Howe and Spalding Source of Information: Morse's "Atlas of the United States on an Improved plan" Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 7.5x9.75 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Kentucky and Tennessee, 1825; 35; ID: 35 Map #: 035 Map Title: Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1825 Cartographer: H.S. Tanner Engraver: H.S. Tanner and Assistants Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: H.S. Tanner Source of Information: Tanner's "New American Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 20x27.5 Notes: 1825 edition of 1823 map Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Geographischstatistische und historische Charte von Tennessee, [1824- 1828]; 36; ID: 36 Map #: 036 Map Title: Geographischstatistische und historische Charte von Tennessee Date of Creation: [1824- 1828] Cartographer: Henry Charles Carey and I. Lea Engraver: Place of Publication: Weimar, Germany Publisher: Im Verlage dea Geographischen Instituts Source of Information: Carl Ferdinand Weiland's "Atlas von Amerika" Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 10.75x18.25 Notes: Based on a map of Tennessee in Carey and Lea's "Complete, Historical, Chronologic al and Geographic al American Atlas" published in 1822 Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer
- Tennessee, [1824]; 37; ID: 37 Map #: 037 Map Title: Tennessee Date of Creation: [1824] Cartographer: Anthony Finley Engraver: Young and Delleker Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Anthony Finley Source of Information: Finley's "New General Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 8.5x11.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Tennessee, [1825]; 38; ID: 38 Map #: 038 Map Title: Tennessee Date of Creation: [1825] Cartographer: Anthony Finley Engraver: Young and Delleker Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Anthony Finley Source of Information: Finley's "New General Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 8.5x11.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Tennessee, [1824]; 39; ID: 39 Map #: 039 Map Title: Tennessee Date of Creation: [1824] Cartographer: Engraver: Young and Delleker Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Anthony Finley Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 8.5x11.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Compiled from the latest Authorities, ca. 1826; 40; ID: 40 Map #: 040 Map Title: Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Compiled from the latest Authorities Date of Creation: ca. 1826 Cartographer: D.H. Vance Engraver: J.H. Young Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Anthony Finley Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 17x21.75 Notes: Shows statistical table Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Compiled from the latest Authorities, ca. 1826; 41; ID: 41 Map #: 041 Map Title: Map of Kentucky and Tennessee Compiled from the latest Authorities Date of Creation: ca. 1826 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Flint's "Geography and History of the Western States" Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 16.5x21 Notes: Includes statistical table. Backed on linen Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Tennessee, [1829]; 42; ID: 42 Map #: 042 Map Title: Tennessee Date of Creation: [1829] Cartographer: Anthony Finley Engraver: Young and Delleker Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Anthony Finley Source of Information: Finley's "New Geand#96;neral Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 8.5x11.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Map of the States of Kentucky and Tennessee, 1831; 43; ID: 43 Map #: 043 Map Title: Map of the States of Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1831 Cartographer: Engraver: Fenner Sears and Co. Place of Publication: London Publisher: I.T. Hinton and Simpkin and Marshall Source of Information: Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 9.75x15.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Map of the States of Kentucky and Tennessee, 1831; 44; ID: 44 Map #: 044 Map Title: Map of the States of Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1831 Cartographer: Engraver: Fenner Sears and Co. Place of Publication: London Publisher: I.T. Hinton and Simpkin and Marshall Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 9.75x15.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Kentucky and Tennessee, [1832]; 45; ID: 45 Map #: 045 Map Title: Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: [1832] Cartographer: Engraver: J. Knight Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Source of Information: Baird's "View of the Valley of the Mississippi" Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 5x6.5 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Map of the Cumberland River From The Falls to Nashville, 1834; 46; ID: 46 Map #: 046 Map Title: Map of the Cumberland River From The Falls to Nashville Date of Creation: 1834 Cartographer: Matthew Rhea, Randolph Coyle Engraver: Howard Stansbury Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: "Report on The Improvement of that Stream for the navigation ot is by Steam Boat" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 15x28.25 Notes: Framed: No Location: Bottom Drawer
- Survey and Map of the Cumberland River from Cowan's Shoals to Bartlett's Creek Island, 1834; 47; ID: 47 Map #: 047 Map Title: Survey and Map of the Cumberland River from Cowan's Shoals to Bartlett's Creek Island Date of Creation: 1834 Cartographer: Howard Stansbury, John P. Bailey and George O'Driscoll Engraver: Place of Publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Government Printing Office Source of Information: "United States Congress: A Collection of Maps, etc.." Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: Notes: Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Map of the Coal Formation in Tennessee, 1834; 48; ID: 48 Map #: 048 Map Title: Map of the Coal Formation in Tennessee Date of Creation: 1834 Cartographer: Gerard Troost Engraver: Nathanial Currier Place of Publication: New York Publisher: Source of Information: "Report to the State of Tennessee" Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 12x14 Notes: Troost was the state geologist of Tennessee Framed: No Location: Missing
- Tennessee, [1835]; 49; ID: 49 Map #: 049 Map Title: Tennessee Date of Creation: [1835] Cartographer: Bradford Engraver: Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 7.75x10 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Tennessee and Kentucky, ca. 1835; 50; ID: 50 Map #: 050 Map Title: Tennessee and Kentucky Date of Creation: ca. 1835 Cartographer: Engraver: G.W. Boynton and Co. Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: outline color Size of Map: 7.75x10 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Kentucky and Tennessee, 1836; 51; ID: 51 Map #: 051 Map Title: Kentucky and Tennessee Date of Creation: 1836 Cartographer: David H. Burr Engraver: Place of Publication: New York Publisher: Thomas Ulman Source of Information: "American Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 11.5x12 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- A New Map of Tennessee With Its Roads and Distances, [1836]; 52; ID: 52 Map #: 052 Map Title: A New Map of Tennessee With Its Roads and Distances Date of Creation: [1836] Cartographer: H.S. Tanner Engraver: Jand W.W. Warr Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: H.S. Tanner Source of Information: Tanner's "Universal Atlas" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 10.5x14.5 Notes: Insets of Nashville and Knoxville Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Mitchell's Map of Tennessee, ca. 1836; 53; ID: 53 Map #: 053 Map Title: Mitchell's Map of Tennessee Date of Creation: ca. 1836 Cartographer: Engraver: J.H. Young Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: Notes: Housed in a folder Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Tennessee, 1838; 54; ID: 54 Map #: 054 Map Title: Tennessee Date of Creation: 1838 Cartographer: T.G. Bradford Engraver: G.W. Boynton Place of Publication: Publisher: Source of Information: "Illustrated Altas of the United States and Adjacent Countries" Color/Black and White: color Size of Map: 11x15 Notes: Framed: Yes Location: Foyer
- Geological Map of Cocke County, East Tenn., [1840]; 55; ID: 55 Map #: 055 Map Title: Geological Map of Cocke County, East Tenn. Date of Creation: [1840] Cartographer: Gerard Troost Engraver: P.S. Duval Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Source of Information: "5th Geological Report to the General Assembly of Tennessee" Color/Black and White: black and white Size of Map: 11.25x14.75 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer
- Fifth Geological Report to the Twenty-Third General Assembly of Tennessee, 1839; 56; ID: 56 Map #: 055 a Map Title: Fifth Geological Report to the Twenty-Third General Assembly of Tennessee Date of Creation: 1839 Cartographer: Engraver: Place of Publication: Nashville Publisher: J. Geo. Harris Source of Information: Color/Black and White: balck and white Size of Map: 9.5x6 Notes: Author: Gerard Troost. Housed in a folder Framed: No Location: Top Drawer
- Map of the Ocoee District, 1841; 57; ID: 57 Map #: 056 Map Title: Map of the Ocoee District Date of Creation: 1841 Cartographer: Gerard Troost Engraver: Lehman and Duval Place of Publication: Philadelphia Publisher: Source of Information: "4th Report to the State of Tennessee" Color/Black and White: some color Size of Map: 19x21 Notes: Framed: No Location: Middle Drawer